class WritingViewModel {
  int score = 0;

  List<Map> questions = [
    {
      'question': 'Roughly how long, on average, do pet bunnies live? , ',
      'answers': [
        'more tahn 10 years ',
        'less than 5 years',
        '2 years',
        'less than 1 year'
      ],
      'correctAnswer': 'on',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Dogs have such a strong sense of smell that they can sniff out medical issues or problems in humans ?',
      'answers': ['Yes', 'No'],
      'correctAnswer': 'Yes',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Rabbits are social creatures and can become depressed if they’re kept alone as pets ?',
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'True',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Do you like classical music? ----.',
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'True',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Pet birds do not need regular vet checkups ?',
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'False',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Cats live longer when they’re kept outdoors as pets ?',
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'False',
    },
    {
      'question':
          "If they’re cared for properly, pet turtles can live for decades and grow to be a foot long ?",
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'True',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Chinchillas are not nocturnal and are most active during the day ?',
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'False',
    },
    {
      'question': "A pet cat’s lifespan is which of these, generally speaking?",
      'answers': ['20-25 years', '5-10 years', '1-5 years', '12-18 years'],
      'correctAnswer': '12-18 years',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Our blood pressure goes down when we pet a dog, and the dog’s blood pressure goes down, too ?',
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'True',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'A bloodhound’s sense of smell is so accurate that the tracking can be used as evidence in a court of law, according to the AKC ?',
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'True',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Covering a pet bird’s cage at night gives it privacy and often helps keep it calm until morning ?',
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'True',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Cats spend roughly what percentage of their lives sleeping?',
      'answers': ['20%', '50%', '70%', '90%'],
      'correctAnswer': '50',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'During her lifetime, Queen Elizabeth II owned dozens of which type of dog?',
      'answers': [
        'German Shepherd',
        'German Shepherd',
        'German Shepherd',
        'German Shepherd'
      ],
      'correctAnswer': 'German Shepherd',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'When it comes to keeping geckos as pets, male geckos should not be in the same enclosure because they’ll attack each other ?',
      'answers': ['False', 'True'],
      'correctAnswer': 'True',
    },
  ];
}
